Hello. I have a package for you.
Thank you.
This package requires ID.
It must be signed for in person.
Is Fu Yan here?
You like Jacky Cheung too?
Yeah. Why?
No, nothing.
I... I happen to have two
tickets to Jacky Cheung's concert.
I just wanted to ask
if you want to go with me.
Why are you hurting yourself?
Without you, nothing matters anymore.
Don't abandon me.
We have to be together forever.
Why'd you quit so suddenly?
I just need a break.
Are you in some kind of trouble?
Su Juan.
You can completely trust me.
You ask me why
I keep pushing you away.
Actually, I push everyone away.
I know.
Those things
are like a thorn
stuck in my chest.
It's stuck too deep.
I can't pull it out.
Or maybe,
I just don't want to pull it out.
Only that pain
can make me realize
that I'm still alive.
So,
that's also why you refuse to let anyone close.
I'm just that unreasonable.
I know.
That's why I like you.
That's just it.
I'm also an
unreasonable person.
Anyway,
I won't approve your resignation.
I won't let you
bear everything all alone.
I'll arrange a
lighter job for you.
Think about it carefully.
Give yourself a chance.
Juan
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have badmouthed you
behind your back.
It's okay. I didn't take it to heart.
Actually,
I think you're really amazing.
I really like you.
You're a role model to us all.
President Han.
Have you finished your work?
I'm getting to it right now.
Right, right. By the way,
let me show you something.
Today,
the police successfully arrested a
so-called master who has long used superstitious activities
to commit fraud.
I told you.
He's just a fraud.
My mom still doesn't believe it.
spreading superstitious claims about warding off disasters,
President Han, in this world...
The video conference is ready.
You can start whenever you're ready.
under the guise of performing rituals and selling talismans.
Do you believe there are ghosts in this world?
Ghosts? How could there be ghosts in this world?
Fake.
Stay back!
You lied to me again.
I just wanted to respect your choice.
My choice?
Did you ever think
that I never wanted to make these choices?
I know.
But that's not fair to you.
It's the punishment I deserve.
I figured it out recently,
why I was so afraid of losing you.
It's because if I did,
I'd have to face that day.
Doctor.
Even if the surgery is successful,
there will still be aftereffects, right?
Yes.
If only I had known his decision.
I killed you.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear to watch you
live on without dignity.
I couldn't face you like that.
And you couldn't accept
yourself like that, either.
I know.
Stay back!
I don't blame you.
Su Juan.
I forgive you.
But I can't forgive myself.
Juan, you're awake.
Are you alright?
Su Juan.
Who are you talking to?
Sorry.
I'm so tired.
I'm going home.
I'll take you home.
No need, thanks.
Su Juan.
Those experiences
are like
a thorn stuck in my chest.
It's stuck so deep
I can't pull it out at all.
Or maybe
I don't want to pull it out at all.
Because only the pain
reminds me
that I'm still alive.
So
you refuse to get close to anyone.
I'm fine.
This afternoon,
his fingers moved.
Just a normal conditioned reflex.
It doesn't mean much.
Don't give up hope.
Let us know if you need any help.
Bed Two.
How are you doing?
Much better.
Go easy next time.
Alright, you're recovering quite well.
Yeah.
Get ready to be discharged.
Okay, doctor.
Don't keep hogging the bed.
You hear that? Hurry up and get better.
Let me ask you.
I'm asking you, how many is this?
Six.
Six, my ass.
I'm just kidding.
Don't mess with me.
Do you know how exhausted I've been lately?
There's nothing to be nervous about.
Anyway, we're closer than anyone.
Even if I really turn into a fool,
you'll still take care of me, right?
Let me make this clear upfront.
If you fall into a vegetative state,
I definitely won't take care of you.
Being in a vegetative state is great.
Once in a vegetative state,
we can be together forever.
Stop talking nonsense.
I'll stop.
Right.
We're going to be together forever.
Su Juan,
from this day forward,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
for better, for worse,
to love him,
honor him,
protect him,
until the end of your days...
Do you?
I do.